Guide to the Lindbergh Picture Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh family, 1930-circa 1979; Series III
  - Group
    - Circa 1935 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      In North Haven, Maine.
    - 1935 December 31 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Arrival in Liverpool, England.
    - Circa 1937 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      At Long Barn, Kent, England.
    - 1936, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jon Morrow Lindbergh, and Land Morrow Lindbergh in France.
    - Circa 1939 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      In Englewood, New Jersey.
    - Circa 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      At Lloyd Neck Manor House in Long Island, New York.
    - Circa 1940s (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
      File consists of negatives.
    - Circa 1940-1942 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      In Martha's Vineyard, Massachusetts.
    - 1940-1943 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Circa 1942 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Circa 1943-1945 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      In Belwood.
    - Circa 1944 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Album consists of photographs of the Lindbergh children together.
    - Circa 1945-1950s (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Circa 1946 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      In Long Barn, Kent, England.
    - Circa 1947 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Circa 1948 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Anne Spencer Lindbergh and Reeve Morrow Lindbergh.
    - 1949 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh and Anne Spencer Lindbergh.
    - Circa 1950 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Circa 1950-1958 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Circa 1964, circa 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Individual
    - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, Jr., 1930-1932 (Box 25, Folder 1-14)
      See also: Oversize, box 73, folder 1
    - Lindbergh, Jon Morrow, 1932-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1-15)
    - Lindbergh, Land Morrow, Circa 1937-circa 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1-10)
      See also: Oversize, box 73, folder 2
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1941-1975 (Box 27, Folder 11-21)
      See also: Oversize, box 73, folder 3
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow, Circa 1943-circa 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, Circa 1946-circa 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6-10)
      See also: Oversize, box 73, folders 4-5
- Lindbergh/Land/Lodge families, Circa 1840-1978; Series IV
  The series is arranged in two sections: Lindbergh and Land/Lodge. The Lindbergh photographs are arranged alphabetically by last name of subject. In the Land/Lodge section, albums with photographs of multiple individuals are listed first followed by photographs of individuals filed alphabetically by last name.
  The series consists of photographic prints and negatives of various members of Charles Augustus Lindbergh's relatives in the Lindbergh, Land, and Lodge family lines. Oversized photographs are filed in Oversize at the end of the collection.
  - Lindbergh
    - Bolander, Carl, Circa 1915 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Brown family, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Reeve Morrow Lindbergh's children.
    - Butler, Juno Pauline and Linda Alvina Seal, Circa 1880-circa 1900 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Sisters of August Lindbergh.
    - Christie family, 1943-1946 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Eva Lindbergh's husband and their children.
    - Feydy, Anne Spencer Lindbergh, family, 1964-1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Anne Spencer Lindbergh's family.
    - Feydy, Jaqueline, Circa 1964-1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Lindbergh, August, Circa 1873 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Lindbergh, Bertha, Alfred, Ida, and Ingrin, Circa 1860 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Lindbergh, Charles August (portraits), Circa 1884-1910 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
    - Lindbergh, Charles August, Circa 1889-1892 (Box 29, Folder 11-16)
    - Lindbergh, Erik, Circa 1973 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Lindbergh, Erin and Peter, Circa 1964 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Lindbergh, Eva, 1901-1973 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Lindbergh, Eva and Lillian, Circa 1892-1897 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge Land, 1878-1890 (Box 29, Folder 21-22)
      See also: Oversize, box 74, folder 1
    - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge Land, 1892-circa 1940s (Box 30, Folder 1-14)
    - Lindbergh, Frank Albert, Circa 1908 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Lindbergh, Frans, Circa 1950s (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Lindbergh, Jon, family, 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 17-18)
    - Lindbergh, Land, family, 1976 December-1977 January (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Lindbergh, Lillian, 1901-1910 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Lindbergh, Louise Carline, Circa 1902 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Lindbergh, Mans, 1865 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Lindbergh, Mary La Fond, Circa 1896 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      Charles August Lindbergh's first wife.
    - Lindbergh, Morgan, Circa 1973 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      Son of Land Morrow Lindbergh.
    - Lindbergh, Perry, Circa 1830-circa 1936 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Lindbergh, Victor, Circa 1861-1865 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Lindbergh, Wendy, Circa 1957 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Nicols, Hanna, Circa 1927 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      Charles Augustus Lindbergh's aunt.
    - Robbins family, Circa 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Seal family, Circa 1943 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Land/Lodge
    - Land/Lodge family albums
      Additional Land family group photographs are filed under Oversize, Lindbergh/Land/Lodge familes.
      - Carte de visite album, Circa 1850s-1870s (Box 31)
        Includes photographs of Evangeline Lodge Land (?), Edwin Albert Lodge, John C. Lodge (?) and other unidentified family members as well as images of famous individuals.
      - Carte de visite album, 1883 (Box 31)
        Includes photographs of Charles Bird Barrett; Henry Ward Beecher; Jeannie Campbell; Captain Albert M. Edwards; Mrs. Foster; Charles Henry Land, Jr.; Charles Henry Land, Sr.; Clara Land; Evangeline Lodge Land; Frank Land; Mrs. Fred J. Land; Scott Land; Susanne Lander; Mrs. Lindsay and Maude; Charles D. Lodge; Edmund Lodge; Edwin Lodge; Edwin Albert Lodge; Evangeline Lodge; [Hariette Christianna Lodge?]; John Christian Lodge; Laura Lodge; Alzina Sharp; Miss Annie Wakeley; and unidentified individuals.
      - Carte de visite album, 1880s (Box 32)
        Includes photographs of Captain Charles B. Barrett; Eddie Barrett; Ella Lodge Barrett; Evangeline Lodge Land; Gordon Land; Grandfather Land; Harriet Clubb Lodge Lindsay; Albert Lodge; Charles D. Lodge; Christiana Lodge; Edward Augustus Lodge; Edwin Albert Lodge; Harriett Christiana Lodge; John Christian Lodge; Laura Lodge; Nina Sharp; Tommy Tait; and unidentified individuals.
    - Barrett, Dr. Charles Bird, Sr., 1850s-1860s (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Barrett, Charles Bird, Jr., 1880s (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Barrett, Ella Lodge, Circa 1860-1900 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Burkholder, Mrs. (Land) and daughter, Circa 1900 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Chisolm, George King and Isabella, Circa 1841 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Clark, Abigail (Land), Circa 1840s (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Clubb, Baltimore, Circa 1850 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Brother of Harriet (Clubb) Lindsay.
    - De Kaye, Mabel (Land), Circa 1870s (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Daughter of Scott Land.
    - Hoadley, Mary (Kissane), Circa 1870-circa 1900 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Huntemer, Robert and William, Circa 1929 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Land, Alphra Charis, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Land, Charles Henry, Circa 1847-1906 (Box 33, Folder 12-21)
      See also: Oversize, box 74, folder 3
    - Land, Charles Henry, Circa 1907-1915 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
    - Land, Charles Henry, Jr., 1879-1961 (Box 34, Folder 4-11)
      See also: Oversize, box 74, folder 4
    - Land, Ephraim, Circa 1840 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Land, Evangeline Lodge, Circa 1860-1919 (Box 34, Folder 13-15)
      See also: Oversize, box 74, folder 5
    - Land, Francis, Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Land, Frank A., Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Land, Frederick J., Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Land, George, Circa 1910 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Land, John, 1893 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Land, Scott, Circa 1902 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Land, Susan, Circa 1850-1880 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Lindsay, Harriet (Clubb) Lodge, Circa 1840s-1850s (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Lindsay, William, Circa 1840s (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd, Reuben (Kissane), Circa 1910 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Includes photographs of his house.
    - Lodge, Albert, Circa 1860s-1900 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Lodge, Alice Dwight (Berry), Circa 1900-1910 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Lodge, Edwin Albert
      See: Oversize, box 74, folder 6
    - Lodge, Edwin Albert, with sons, Circa 1860s-1907 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Lodge, Harriet Christiana, 1870s-1890s (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Lodge, John Christian, 1862-1950 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Lodge, Laura, Circa 1880s (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rogers, William Kissane, Circa 1870-1910 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Ryan, Clara (Land), Circa 1860s-1870s (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Scott, General Winfield (print), Undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Sharp, Nina, Circa 1870s-1900 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Witherspoon, Emma Aphora (Lodge), Circa 1840s-1880s (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Witherspoon, Emma Bertha, Circa 1840s (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Witherspoon, Henry, Circa 1840s (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Witherspoon, Homer and Roy, 1850s? (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Witherspoon, Captain John, 1860s (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Witherspoon, Captain John, family (portrait)
      See: Oversize, box 74, folder 7
    - Unidentified Lodge/Land family members?, Circa 1860s-1880s (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Morrow/Cutter family, Circa 1873-1979; Series V
  The series is arranged as follows: Morrow family group photographs are listed first, followed by the rest of the photographs in the series filed alphabetically by last name.
  The series consists of photographic prints and negatives primarily depicting Anne Morrow Lindbergh; her parents, Dwight Whitney Morrow and Elizabeth Cutter Morrow; and her siblings, Elisabeth Reeve Morrow, Dwight Whitney Morrow, Jr., and Constance Cutter Morrow. Additional immediate descendants of the family are also included. The bulk of the photographs are dated from approximately 1904 to the mid-1950s and depict family events and trips. Most of the photographs of individuals in the series are portraits. Oversized photographs are filed in Oversize at the end of the collection.
  - Morrow family groups and trips
    - Circa 1904-1918 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Elizabeth Cutter Morrow and Dwight Whitney Morrow with children.
    - Circa 1906-1908 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Morrow family album.
    - Circa 1907 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      On Spring Lane.
    - Circa 1908 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      At Twilight Park.
    - Circa 1908-1920 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Morrow chlidren.
    - "Pictures of our trips to Nassau, Bahamas 1915, 1916, 1917" (album), 1915-1917 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Circa 1917 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Anne and Elisabeth Morrow.
    - Circa 1918 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      In Quissett, Massachusetts.
    - Circa 1920 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      Western U.S. trip.
    - 1924 July 7 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh and Jay Scandrett.
    - Circa 1924 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      In Nassau, Bahamas.
    - Circa 1926 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Elizabeth Cutter Morrow and Dwight Whitney Morrow with relatives (some unidentified).
    - Circa 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Trip to Mexico.
    - Circa 1926-1932 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Some include Charles Augustus Lindbergh.
    - Circa 1930s (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Circa 1935 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      With Harold and Ben Nicolson.
    - Circa 1935 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Circa 1935-1940 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 1948-1953 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      See also: Oversize, box 75, folders 6-10
      Consists of Christmas cards depicting Elizabeth Cutter Morrow with her grandchildren.
    - 1949 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      In Mexico, mostly Elizabeth Cutter Morrow and miscellaneous scenes.
    - Circa 1950 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      The Morrow's Mexican fair in Englewood, New Jersey.
    - Circa 1951 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Circa 1954 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      Atchley pictures.
    - Circa 1954 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      In Mexico.
    - Unidentified negatives, Undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Caldwell, Louis Roberts, 1975 May 6 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Cutter, Anne E., Circa 1880s-1910 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Fulenwider, Anne and Wendy, Circa 1973-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Kenney-McIlvaine family, Circa 1920s-1970s (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Morgan, Aubrey N., Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, David, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Morrow, Agnes (Scandrett), Circa 1880-1930 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Morrow, Anne and Betty, Circa 1910-1920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Morrow, Clara, Circa 1910s-1920s (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Morrow, Constance Cutter, Circa 1914-1940s (Box 38, Folder 10)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 2
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Sr., Circa 1894-1937 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 3
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Sr. and Jr., Circa 1911-1932 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney Jr., Circa 1916-1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 4
  - Morrow, Elizabeth, Rhidian and Sarah, Circa 1950s (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter and Mary Cutter, Circa 1873-1881 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, Circa 1881-1904 (Box 38, Folder 16-20)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, Circa 1906-1954 (Box 39, Folder 1-17)
    Includes portraits and photographs with family members.
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folders 5-10
  - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve, Circa 1904-1933 (Box 39, Folder 18-20)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 11
  - Morrow, Hilda, Circa 1893-1900 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Morrow, James E., Circa 1880s-1900 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    Dwight Whitney Morrow, Sr.'s father.
  - Morrow, Jay, with Katherine Leighton, 1880s-1937 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 12
  - Morrow, Stephen, Circa 1939 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Prosser, Anna-Fey, Circa 1920s (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Scandrett, Jay, Rebecca, and Richard, 1905-1970s (Box 39, Folder 26)
    See also: Oversize, box 75, folder 13
  - Williams, Faith (Morrow), 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    Includes her husband and children.
  - Unidentified Morrow family?, Undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Friends, acquaintances, and others, Circa 1870-1979; Series VI
  The series is arranged alphabetically by last name or first name if last name is unknown.
  The series consists of photographic prints depicting individuals not included in the previous series and are primarily friends and acquaintances of Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh. Friends and acquaintances of other members of the Lindbergh, Land, Lodge and Morrow families are also included. Additionally, some of the individuals depicted in the photographs may have had no relation to the Lindberghs, but may have merely sent their photographs to the Lindberghs or the Lindberghs may have collected the photographs out of personal interest.
  - Alexis, Dom, 1960s (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - [Alfort?], Dr.
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 1
  - Ames, Amyas, 1977 January 26 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Anders, William, Borman, Frank, and Lovell, James, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Apollo 8 astronauts.
  - Anne?, Circa 1950s (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Arnold, H. H., 1939 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Atchley, Dana, Circa 1950s (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Balchen, Bernt, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Beauregard, Nettie, Circa 1930s (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Beckstrand, Elmer, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Beisil, Rex B., Circa 1930s (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Bigelow, Poultney, Circa 1936 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Biltz, Jeanne, Circa 1950s (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Bixby, Harold, Circa 1930s (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Bolton, Francis, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Burnett, Charles T., 1923 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Carrel, Alexis, Circa 1936 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Cary family, 1976-1979 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - [Cash, Mrs.?], Circa 1880-1885 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Chapin school friends, Circa 1920s (Box 40, Folder 19-20)
  - Clark, Louise, and friends, Circa 1901-1927 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    On the Sorosis House lawn with Florence Dillon, Sarah Mckenzie, Lillian Steele, Maud Thayer, Clara Turner and Lila Turner.
  - Corning, Winifred, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - [Coultas, Mrs.?], 1914 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Dam, Mrs. and Mr., at Long Barn, 1930s (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Daugherty, Neil, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Deighton, Edward Blair, Circa 1920s (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Doolittle, Jimmy, 1902-1905 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Earhart, Amelia, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    Includes a photograph tentatively identified as Earhart with Charles Augustus Lindbergh and a photograph of a painting of Earhart.
  - Ebeling, Dr. A. H., 1958 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Fisch, Isadore, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Ford, Henry, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 2
  - Gilchrist family, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Gorman, Arthur, Circa 1910s (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Gow, Betty, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Guggenheim, Diane, Circa 1929 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 3
  - H__, Margaret, Circa 1930s (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Hauptmann, Anna
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 4
  - Hawks, Frank, 1930 April 7 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Circa 1940s (Box 40, Folder 36)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 5
  - Herrick, Myron T. (painting of), Circa 1930 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 6
  - Hitler, Adolph, Circa 1942 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Hodan family, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Hook, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Hooker, Circa 1920s (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Hosegawa family, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Humberstone, Harry Bruce, Circa 1870-1900 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Hungerford, Dorothy, Circa 1906 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Koff, Anne, Norman, and Sally, Circa 1930 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Larson, Bruce, Circa 1960 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Liggett School, 1890 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lisa, Circa 1920s (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Love, Phillip R., 1926-1943 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 7
  - Lynch, Arthur, 1927 May 15 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Macnab, Sandy, Circa 1940s (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Maddox, Jennie W., Circa 1940s? (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Marion
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 8
  - [McCormick?], Robert N.
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 9
  - Melcher, John Rodman, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Anna, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Milles, Carl, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, Billy, Circa 1920s (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Monot family, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Nelson, Thomas P., 1927 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Neville, Edwin L., Circa 1960s (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Nicolson, Harold, Circa 1935 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - North Commission Alaska Conservation Committee, 1968 April 8 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Nygord, Lillian (?), Circa 1930s (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - O'Brian, Timmy, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Peralta, Angela, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Peters-Solmar, Kuno, 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Preussner, Regina, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Robertson, James L., 1927 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller, Harry and Laurance, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Circa 1936 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Rodewald family, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Ruth, Harold, Jackie, and Butch, Circa 1960s (Box 41, Folder 26)
    Album sent to Anne Morrow Lindbergh.
  - Saunders, Jean, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Scheyer children, 1950s? (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Scott, O. E., Circa 1930 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Sevina, Nola, 1936-1938 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Sikorsky, Igor, 1940, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    Includes photographs of Sikorsky testing his helicopter.
  - Smith, Colonel Truman
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 10
  - Snider, Robert L., Circa 1948 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Spalding, Edward Bartlett
    See: Oversize, box 76, folder 11
  - Stevens, Bob and Dorothy, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Stokes (?), Circa 1920s (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Sypkens, Stephanie M., 1940 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - [Taquey?], Kitty, 1966 December 17 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Thomas, Jackie, Circa 1940-1950 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Udet, Ernst, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Vance, Betsy, Circa 1950 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Winburn family, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Yates family, 1967 December 13 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified, Circa 1900-circa 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
    See also: Oversize, box 76, folder 12
- Topical, 1880-1983; Series VII
  The series is arranged in four sections: Places, Spirit of St. Louis, Aviation general, and Miscellany. With the exception of the Spirit of St. Louis section, which is arranged chronologically, the sections are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  The series consists of photographic and art prints arranged by topic. Of particular note are the aviation related photographs including those of the Spirit of St. Louis (without Charles Augustus Lindbergh), early Lockheed, Sikorsky, and Curtiss airplanes; and pioneer aviators. A photograph of Charles Augustus Lindbergh's perfusion pump is filed under Miscellany.
  - Places
    - Africa, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      All used in Anne Morrow Lindbergh's book Earth Shine.
    - Africa, Circa 1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 1
    - Arctic Circle
      See: Oversize, box 77, folder 2
    - Nassau, Bahamas, Circa 1920s (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Tumucumaque, Brazil, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Baker Lake, Canada, Circa 1956 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Cornwall, England, Circa 1930s (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Durham, England, 1930s? (Box 43, Folder 7)
      World War I ruins.
    - Kent, England (Long Barn), Circa 1930s (Box 43, Folder 8-10)
    - Kent, England (Sandwich Bay), Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - London, England, 1937 November 25 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      King George's funeral.
    - London, England, Circa 1930s (Box 43, Folder 13)
      London Bridge and The Cheshire Cheese pub.
    - Sevenoaks, England, Circa 1930s (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Illiec, France, Circa 1938 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Mont Saint Michel, France, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - St. Gildas, France, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Germany, Circa 1940s (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Bad Harzburg, Germany, Circa 1930s (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Bavaria, Germany, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Berlin, Germany, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Potsdam, Germany, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Rhodes, Greece, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Greenland, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Godthaab, Greenland, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - India, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Japan, Circa 1960s-1970s (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
    - Mexico, 1920s-1950s (Box 44, Folder 12-20)
    - Black Island, New Guinea, Circa 1944 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Panama, 1928? (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - Luzon, Philippines, 1972? (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Siam, Thailand, Circa 1938 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - United States
      - Alaska, 1930s (?) (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Appalachian Trail, Circa 1930-1949 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Arizona, 1929-1933 (Box 45, Folder 8-9)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 2
      - California, 1916-1917 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 3
      - Colorado, 1880, circa 1944 (Box 45, Folder 11-12)
        See also: Oversize, box 77, folder 4
      - Connecticut, Circa 1940s (Box 45, Folder 13-15)
      - Florida, Undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Hawaii, Circa 1970-1974 (Box 45, Folder 17-18)
      - Illinois, Circa 1898 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Kansas, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Maine, 1930s (Box 46, Folder 3-8)
      - Maryland, Circa 1908-1915 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Massachusetts, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 10)